export const DummyData = [
  {
    SetName: "New Question set",
    SubjectName: "Mathematics",
    SetQuestion: [
      {
        Question: "4+4",
        Answer: "8",
      },
      {
        Question: "10+4",
        Answer: "12",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    SetName: "New Question set",
    SubjectName: "Mathematics2",
    SetQuestion: [
      {
        Question: "4+4",
        Answer: "8",
      },
      {
        Question: "10+4",
        Answer: "12",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    SetName: "New Question set",
    SubjectName: "Mathematics",
    SetQuestion: [
      {
        Question: "4+4",
        Answer: "8",
      },
      {
        Question: "10+4",
        Answer: "12",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    SetName: "New Question set",
    SubjectName: "Mathematics",
    SetQuestion: [
      {
        Question: "4+4",
        Answer: "8",
      },
      {
        Question: "10+4",
        Answer: "12",
      },
      {
        Question: "4+4",
        Answer: "8",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    SetName: "New Question set",
    SubjectName: "Mathematics",
    SetQuestion: [
      {
        Question: "4+4",
        Answer: "8",
      },
      {
        Question: "10+4",
        Answer: "12",
      },
    ],
  },
];
